export default {
  id: 'mid_1_1b',
  name: '상용한자(중학1/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:끼일/음:かい', answer: ['介'] },
    { question: '독:かさ/음:さん', answer: ['傘'] },
    { question: '독:척추/음:せき', answer: ['脊'] },
    { question: '독:こ(む)、こ(める)/음:', answer: ['込'] },
    { question: '독:일/음:た', answer: ['汰'] },
    { question: '독:실을/음:だ', answer: ['駄'] },
    { question: '독:さく/음:', answer: ['咲'] },
    { question: '독:나/음:ちん', answer: ['朕'] },
    { question: '독:도울/음:ふ', answer: ['扶'] },
    { question: '독:か(える)、か(わる)/음:たい', answer: ['替'] },
    { question: '독:ひそ(む)、もぐ(る)/음:せん', answer: ['潜'] },
    { question: '독:ぬ(く)、ぬ(ける)、ぬ(かす)、ぬ(かる)/음:ばつ', answer: ['抜'] },
    { question: '독:かみ/음:はつ', answer: ['髪'] },
    { question: '독:ふ(せる)、ふ(す)/음:ふく', answer: ['伏'] },
    { question: '독:つ(く)/음:とつ', answer: ['突'] },
    { question: '독:감옥/음:ごく', answer: ['獄'] },
    { question: '독:けもの/음:じゅう', answer: ['獣'] },
    { question: '독:희롱할/음:がん', answer: ['玩'] },
    { question: '독:ひき/음:ひつ', answer: ['匹'] },
    { question: '독:이길/음:こく', answer: ['克'] },
    { question: '독:まくら/음:', answer: ['枕'] },
    { question: '독:しず(む)、しず(める)/음:ちん', answer: ['沈'] },
    { question: '독:상황/음:きょう', answer: ['況'] },
    { question: '독:のろ(う)/음:じゅ', answer: ['呪'] },
    { question: '독:검열할/음:えつ', answer: ['閲'] },
    { question: '독:기쁠/음:えつ', answer: ['悦'] },
    { question: '독:するど(い)/음:えい', answer: ['鋭'] },
    { question: '독:ぬ(ぐ)、ぬ(げる)/음:だつ', answer: ['脱'] },
    { question: '독:つぶ/음:りゅう', answer: ['粒'] },
    { question: '독:끌고갈/음:ら', answer: ['拉'] },
    { question: '독:보통/음:ふ', answer: ['普'] },
    { question: '독:족보/음:ふ', answer: ['譜'] },
    { question: '독:つちか(う)/음:ばい', answer: ['培'] },
    { question: '독:모실/음:ばい', answer: ['陪'] },
    { question: '독:배상할/음:ばい', answer: ['賠'] },
    { question: '독:쪼갤/음:ぼう', answer: ['剖'] },
    { question: '독:기억할/음:おく', answer: ['憶'] },
    { question: '독:가슴/음:おく', answer: ['臆'] },
    { question: '독:드러날/음:しょう', answer: ['彰'] },
    { question: '독:うるお(う)、うるお(す)、うる(む)/음:じゅん', answer: ['潤'] },
    { question: '독:やみ/음:', answer: ['闇'] },
    { question: '독:한가할/음:かん', answer: ['閑'] },
    { question: '독:たつ/음:りゅう', answer: ['竜'] },
    { question: '독:たき/음:', answer: ['滝'] },
    { question: '독:かご、こも(る)/음:ろう', answer: ['籠'] },
    { question: '독:おそ(う)/음:しゅう', answer: ['襲'] },
    { question: '독:정실/음:ちゃく', answer: ['嫡'] },
    { question: '독:つ(む)/음:てき', answer: ['摘'] },
    { question: '독:しずく、したた(る)/음:てき', answer: ['滴'] },
    { question: '독:임금/음:てい', answer: ['帝'] },
    { question: '독:し(まる)、し(める)/음:てい', answer: ['締'] },
    { question: '독:あきら(める)/음:てい', answer: ['諦'] },
    { question: '독:かたわ(ら)/음:ぼう', answer: ['傍'] },
    { question: '독:から(い)/음:しん', answer: ['辛'] },
    { question: '독:재상/음:さい', answer: ['宰'] },
    { question: '독:と(る)/음:しつ、しゅう', answer: ['執'] },
    { question: '독:잡을/음:し', answer: ['摯'] },
    { question: '독:종/음:ぼく', answer: ['僕'] },
    { question: '독:칠/음:ぼく', answer: ['撲'] },
    { question: '독:열흘/음:じゅん、(しゅん)', answer: ['旬'] },
    { question: '독:따라죽을/음:じゅん', answer: ['殉'] },
    { question: '독:잡을/음:こう', answer: ['拘'] },
    { question: '독:こま/음:', answer: ['駒'] },
    { question: '독:だ(く)、いだ(く)、かか(える)/음:ほう', answer: ['抱'] },
    { question: '독:あわ/음:ほう', answer: ['泡'] },
    { question: '독:대포/음:ほう', answer: ['砲'] },
    { question: '독:세포/음:ほう', answer: ['胞'] },
    { question: '독:あ(きる)、あ(かす)/음:ほう', answer: ['飽'] },
    { question: '독:굽을/음:こう', answer: ['勾'] },
    { question: '독:にお(う)/음:', answer: ['匂'] },
    { question: '독:く(む)/음:しゃく', answer: ['酌'] },
    { question: '독:つ(る)/음:ちょう', answer: ['釣'] },
    { question: '독:꾸짖을/음:かつ', answer: ['喝'] },
    { question: '독:かわく/음:かつ', answer: ['渇'] },
    { question: '독:갈색/음:かつ', answer: ['褐'] },
    { question: '독:くず/음:かつ', answer: ['葛'] },
    { question: '독:かか(げる)/음:けい', answer: ['掲'] },
    { question: '독:뵐, 아뢸/음:えつ', answer: ['謁'] },
    { question: '독:ふ(く)/음:すい', answer: ['吹'] },
    { question: '독:た(く)/음:すい', answer: ['炊'] },
    { question: '독:마음대로/음:し', answer: ['恣'] },
    { question: '독:[いばら]/음:', answer: ['茨'] },
    { question: '독:はか(る)/음:し', answer: ['諮'] },
    { question: '독:ぬす(む)/음:とう', answer: ['盗'] },
    { question: '독:うらや(む)、うらや(ましい)/음:せん', answer: ['羨'] },
    { question: '독:は/음:じん', answer: ['刃'] },
    { question: '독:しの(ぶ)、しの(ばせる)/음:にん', answer: ['忍'] },
    { question: '독:어찌/음:な', answer: ['那'] },
    { question: '독:め(す)/음:しょう', answer: ['召'] },
    { question: '독:ぬま/음:しょう', answer: ['沼'] },
    { question: '독:이을/음:しょう', answer: ['紹'] },
    { question: '독:みことのり/음:しょう', answer: ['詔'] },
    { question: '독:훔칠/음:せつ', answer: ['窃'] },
    { question: '독:おびや(かす)、おど(す)、おど(かす)/음:きょう', answer: ['脅'] },
    { question: '독:わき/음:', answer: ['脇'] },
    { question: '독:か(ける)、か(かる)/음:か', answer: ['架'] },
    { question: '독:후릴, 유괴할/음:かい', answer: ['拐'] },
    { question: '독:おと(る)/음:れつ', answer: ['劣'] },
    { question: '독:ほどこ(す)/음:し、せ', answer: ['施'] }
  ]
}
